thediamondgames.com 2010-11-18

# Privacy Policy | Diamond Games

Please take a moment to read our privacy policy prior to using this Website.

This privacy statement (“Privacy Policy”) covers all the websites owned, affiliated or operated by The Diamond Games, LLC. (“Diamond Games”, “we”, “us”, “our”). Diamond Games knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Diamond Games websites, submitting information or using any of our products or services, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

We want to share with you how we treat personal information about you that we receive in connection with this Website.

Also, note that use of this Website is governed by the Terms of Services posted on the Website. As noted in the Terms of Services, Diamond Games expressly excludes any representation or warranty, express or implied, with respect to the information available on this Website. Diamond Games makes no representation about any third-party websites that may be accessed via links from this Website. By using this Website, you agree that the laws of the District of Columbia, without regard to its conflict of laws principles, will govern all matters between you and Diamond Games with respect to your use of this Website.

What does Diamond Games do?

Diamond Games is an online web site dedicated to casual games. We post reviews, previews, news, and articles about casual games and provide links to download these games. In addition, we let you post your own ratings and reviews on casual games in the comment sections of the web pages.

What Information We Collect and How We Use It.

In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, in order to provide the best online service and enrich our members’ experience, as described further below, sections of this Website may request and display some of your personal information to other members and visitors. Diamond Games members can change their profile information at any time and can control how we and other members communicate with them.

Diamond Games collects personal information that you may submit to us for such purposes as becoming a member of Diamond Games and registering for the use of certain restricted portions of this Website. We use this information to help authenticate users of Diamond Games, send you and other members newsletters and notifications regarding our services, respond to your requests for information or other materials, conduct internal analyses such as surveys, and help you to identify and communicate with other members. Our use of email addresses is discussed in greater detail below in the section entitled “What About Email Addresses.” Note, only your “user name” which you pick is displayed on this Web site. Your full name is never revealed by Diamond Games to other members (unless you expressively pick it as your user name).

Diamond Games has a general policy of not disclosing your personal information to third parties unless you have consented to such sharing. However, we may share the personal information you provide to us with trusted companies we have hired to provide services for us, such as sending out newsletters, developing new Web site features, or collecting or processing information on our behalf. These companies – our vendors – are contractually bound to use personal information that we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide.

In addition, through certain technologies, Diamond Games also collects non-personally-identifiable information from users and visitors to this site. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and targeted advertisements to members. For more information on how we collect this type of information, please see the section below entitled “What about Cookies.”

User profile information which may include your picture and user name (that you provide us) is displayed to other members in order to facilitate user interaction within the Diamond Games community. You can modify and change your personal information at any time by logging into your account, going to your my Diamond Games page, and clicking “Edit my Account.”

What About Email Addresses?

When you provide your email address, we may use it for the purposes of facilitating your invitations to new friends (“Invitees”) to join Diamond Games, inviting “friends” to connect to your personal My Diamond Games page, and sending notifications and other communications related to the Services, such as, for example, newsletters, emailing an article to a friend, or other information. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, or emailing an article to a friend, we will not share or display your email address. We will only do the above is initiated by the user.

Diamond Games members can invite Invitees to join the service by sending emails via our automated invitation system. Diamond Games does not sell the email addresses of Invitees and uses them solely for the internal purposes of sending email invitations and invitation reminders.

Can I Opt Out of Emails?

Members who no longer wish to receive notifications or other communications via email may opt out of such communications. All communications via email include an opt-out link which you may click to unsubscribe from further communications via that channel. You may also visit our [Diamond Games Newsletter page](http://www.thediamondgames.com/newsletter/) to enter your email address into the unsubscribe form and click submit to remove that email address from further communications via that channel.

What about Cookies?

A “cookie” is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. We may use cookies in order to collect certain information about you, such as IP addresses (e.g., whether you are logged on from a .com, .gov, or .edu domain), domain names (the Internet address of a computer), browser type, and the type of computer and operating system being used. Diamond Games uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information to ensure that visitors are provided with a customized content and advertising experience. We record your IP address for security and monitoring purposes.

We do not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to change your cookie settings. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features available on this Website. To disable all cookies, follow the instructions for your particular browser.

Customized Advertisements, Promotions, and Sweepstakes

Ads appearing on this Website may be delivered to users by Diamond Games or one of our Web advertising partners. As noted above, we may use cookies to provide you with customized, targeted ads. Our Web advertising partners may also set cookies to allow their ad servers to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information such as whether you saw their advertisements and which ads you “clicked” on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Please note, however, that this privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Diamond Games on this website and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

In addition, from time to time, Diamond Games or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstakes or contest on Diamond Games. If you voluntarily participate in these activities, you may be asked to provide personal information including your name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. If you participate in a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest, we may transfer personal information to our ad partners who have sponsored the promotions, sweepstakes, or contests. It will be clear at the point of collection whether Diamond Games or one of our sponsors or advertising partners is collecting your personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Links to Third Party Web Sites

We may provide links to third party websites as a convenience to you. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Diamond Games. Diamond Games is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on these linked sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy posted on that linked site.

Public Information

Whenever you voluntarily post public information anywhere on the Diamond Games Web site, people can access that information and in turn could use that information to send you unsolicited communications. Do not post information you consider to be private on this Website if you desire to maintain the privacy of that information.

How Old Should I Be?

The age is 13 or above. Diamond Games does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

Security

At Diamond Games, your privacy and security are our top priorities. Accounts are secured by member-created passwords.

Diamond Games takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database and restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.

PLEASE NOTE: we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.

Privacy and Sharing

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Diamond Games will never disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Diamond Games, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Diamond Games Terms of Use Agreement and to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the Diamond Games service.

Diamond Games reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of all or substantially all of Diamond Games’ assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the “Changes in Our Privacy Policy” section below.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit Diamond Games, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this [Privacy Policy](http://www.thediamondgames.com/privacy-policy/) and our [Terms of Services](http://www.thediamondgames.com/terms-of-service/), including limitation of damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of District of Columbia law.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy

We may make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will inform users of any changes we make by posting a notice on our Website. USERS WILL ALWAYS BE AWARE OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT VIA THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

If the change in how we collect and use information is minor, you will be bound to our privacy policy when you use the site after the changes have been posted. For all material changes to our privacy policy we will provide you with 30 days’ notice through a posting on our Website. At that time, you will have the opportunity to opt out of such new collection and use practices on a going forward basis. Therefore, we recommend that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time to see how any changes impact you.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy, feel free to contact us at privacypolicy@thediamondgames.com or at

The Diamond Games, LLC  
ATTN: Privacy Policy  
PO Box 32249  
Washington DC 20007  
**  
The Effective date of this Privacy Policy: June 30, 2008**

### Game Offers from Our Partners
